[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2002 film is based on the Capcom video game.", "correct_answer": "Resident Evil", "incorrect_answers": ["Meat Market", "House of the Dead", "Area 51"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After appearing in movies like Arachnophobia and Speed actor Jeff Daniels starred in this 1994 Farrelly brothers film.", "correct_answer": "Dumb and Dumber", "incorrect_answers": ["Something Wild", "Kingpin", "Fargo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What river in North America provides food for the largest wintering Bald Eagle population in the continental United States?", "correct_answer": "Skagit River", "incorrect_answers": ["Fraser", "Skeena", "St. Lawrence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "You know, theres like a butt-load of gangs at this school. This one kept wanting me to join because Im pretty good with a bo staff.  In which movie can this line be heard?", "correct_answer": "Napoleon Dynamite", "incorrect_answers": ["Office Space", "The Simpsons Movie", "Hair Spray"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How did fictional character Han Solo win the Millennium Falcon?", "correct_answer": "He won it in a sabacc game.", "incorrect_answers": ["It was given to him.", "He won it in a bet.", "He stole it."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the length of the longest fingernails.", "correct_answer": "24.60 feet (7.5 m)", "incorrect_answers": ["14.10 feet (4.3 m)", "10.49 feet (3.2 m)", "27.23 feet (8.3 m)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which collective noun denotes a group of owls?", "correct_answer": "parliament", "incorrect_answers": ["descent", "dule", "covey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What city is home of Broadway Theatre?", "correct_answer": "New York", "incorrect_answers": ["Washington", "Boston", "New Orleans"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What did Jean Michel Jarre, Ernest Hemingway, Mark Twain, Lord Byron, and Sir Winston Churchill all have for pets?", "correct_answer": "Cats", "incorrect_answers": ["Birds", "Horses", "Dogs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year did the film What About Bob? come out?", "correct_answer": "1991", "incorrect_answers": ["1987", "1989", "1993"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to Grant Taylors wife in the movie Facing the Giants after Grant creates his new philosophy?", "correct_answer": "She gets pregnant.", "incorrect_answers": ["She becomes a writer.", "None of these", "She survives a car accident."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Tom Hanks, who starred in The DaVinci Code,\u201d stars in another movie based on a Dan Brown novel. In Angels and Demons, he plays the same character as in \u201cThe Da Vinci Code. What is this character?", "correct_answer": "Robert Langdon", "incorrect_answers": ["Harry Regan", "Regan Landsford", "Richard Lawrence"]}]